A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.29 (A2003) FA490
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2003.039: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1994-2003; AC.2003.039; 7.86 Cubic Feet 6 standard record storage boxes, R3552-R3557
  - Arts and Humanities (AH), AC.2003.039.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - AH 9825 - SOCIETY FOR THE PRESERVATION OF WEEKSVILLE AND BEDFORD STUYVESANT HISTORY - STABILIZATION AND EXPANSION, 1998 (Box R3552)
    - AH 9827 - DISTRICT CURATORS - "PERFORMANCE PORTRAITS" PROJECT, 1998 (Box R3552)
    - AH 9828; AH 9901 - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (LOS ANGELES) - THE MARCUS GARVEY AND UNIVERSAL NEGRO IMPROVEMENT ASSOCIATION PAPERS, 1993-2001 (Box R3552)
    - AH 9906 - CITY PARKS FOUNDATION - 1999 CENTRAL PARK SUMMERSTAGE FESTIVAL (Box R3552)
    - RF 97055 #118; AH 9809 - SPANISH THEATRE REPERTORY - HUMANITIES PROGRAMS OF "CUBATEATRO" PROJECT, 1997-2002 (Box R3552)
  - Agricultural Sciences (AS), AC.2003.039.2; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - AS 9418 - INTERNATIONAL MAIZE AND WHEAT IMPROVEMENT CENTER (CIMMYT)(MEXICO) - INFORMATION MANAGEMENT STAFF TRAINING, 1994-1999 (Box R3553)
    - AS 9544 - CORNELL UNIVERSITY - HUMAN RESOURCE CAPACITY WITHIN ZIMBABWE SMALLHOLDER SECTOR, 1995-2000 (Box R3553)
    - AS 9706 - UNITED STATES - AGRICULTURE (DEPT. OF) - PLANT AND ANIMAL GENOME VI MEETING, 1997-1998 (Box R3553)
    - AS 9707 - SOIL AND WATER CONSERVATION SOCIETY - SYMPOSIUM ON ECOSYSTEM MANAGEMENT IN A WATERSHED CONTEXT, 1997-1999 (Box R3553)
    - AS 9728 - UNIVERSITY OF NAIROBI (KENYA) - MAIZE-LEGUME BASED CROPPING SYSTEMS, 1997-2000 (Box R3553)
    - AS 9801 - KASETSART UNIVERSITY (THAILAND) - CASSAVA BIOTECHNOLOGY ' TRAINING FOR SALAK PHANSIRI, 1997-2001 (Box R3553)
    - AS 9805 - EPIDAVROS PROJECT - DOCUMENTARY FILM ON AFRICAN DEVELOPMENT, 1997-1999 (Box R3553)
    - AS 9806 - UNIVERSITY OF MALAWI - STRENGTHEN INFORMATION SERVICES, 1991-1999 (Box R3553)
    - AS 9809 - UNITED STATES - AGRICULTURE (DEPT. OF) - PLANT AND ANIMAL GENOME VII MEETING, 1998-1999 (Box R3553)
    - AS 9810 - PURDUE UNIVERSITY - WORKSHOP ON SUSTAINABLE CROP PRODUCTION IN TROPICS AND OTHER WORLD SOIL PROBLEMS, 1998-1999 (Box R3553)
    - AS 9818 - INTERNATIONAL SERVICE FOR NATIONAL AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH (NETHERLANDS) - "BIOTECHNOLOGY FOR AFRICAN CROPS", 1998-2000 (Box R3553)
    - AS 9821 - UNIVERSITY OF NEBRASKA (LINCOLN) - SYMPOSIUM, "POST-GREEN REVOLUTION TRENDS IN CROP YIELD POTENTIAL", 1998-1999 (Box R3553)
    - AS 9825 - KENYA AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH INSTITUTE - BOOK ON BUILDING NATIONAL AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH SYSTEMS IN AFRICA, 1997-1998 (Box R3553)
    - AS 9826 - TROPICAL SOIL BIOLOGY AND FERTILITY PROGRAMME - WORKSHOP ON TROPICAL SOIL BIOLOGY FOR AFRICAN AGRICULTURE, 1998-2002 (Box R3553)
    - AS 9827 - WANGAI, ANNE - GROUNDNUT VIRUSES IN AFRICA, 1997-1999 (Box R3553)
    - AS 9830 - INTERNATIONAL LIVESTOCK RESEARCH INSTITUTE (KENYA) - DAIRY POLICY IN UGANDA, 1998-2002 (Box R3553)
    - AS 9833 - INTERNATIONAL CENTER FOR INFORMATION ON COVER CROPS (HONDURAS) - WORLDWIDE SURVEY ON GREEN MANURE/COVER CROPS AMONG SMALLHOLDERS, 1998-2000 (Box R3553)
    - AS 9834 - UNIVERSIDAD AUTONOMA DE CHIAPAS (MEXICO) - MAIZE-LEGUME SYSTEMS IN THE STATE OF CHIAPAS, 1994-1999 (Box R3553)
    - AS 9836 - MALAWI - AGRICULTURE AND IRRIGATION (MINISTRY OF) - REVIEW OF MAIZE PRODUCTIVITY TASK FORCE, 1998 (Box R3553)
    - AS 9837 - INTERNATIONAL NETWORK FOR THE IMPROVEMENT OF BANANA AND PLANTAIN (FRANCE) - WORKSHOP ON BANANA/PLANTAI N PRODUCTION IN EASTERN/SOUTHERN AFRICA, 1997-2000 (Box R3553)
    - AS 9842 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE FOR RESEARCH IN AGROFORESTRY (KENYA) - UGANDAN PHOSPHATES AND P-DEFICIENT SOIL IN WESTERN KENYA, 1998-2003 (Box R3553)
    - AS 9843 - INTERNATIONAL MAIZE AND WHEAT IMPROVEMENT CENTER (MEXICO) - WORKSHOP ON DROUGHT TOLERANCE IN CEREALS, 1998-2000 (Box R3553)
    - AS 9846 - UNIVERSITY OF COSTA RICA - USE OF GREEN MANURES AND COVER CROPS BY FARMERS IN CENTRAL AMERICA, 1999 (Box R3553)
    - AS 9902 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - INTEGRATED SOIL NUTRIENT MANAGEMENT IN THE SOUTHERN AFRICA REGION, 1998-1999 (Box R3554)
    - AS 9903 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - INDIAN SEED EXPORT TO AFRICA, 1998-1999 (Box R3554)
    - AS 9907 - BONGER, TENKIR - REPORT ON CHINYIKA RESETTLEMENT SCHEME, ZIMBABWE, 1999 (Box R3554)
    - AS 9908 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - ECONOMIC COST OF DROUGHT ON GRAIN PRODUCTION IN ASIA, 1998-2000 (Box R3554)
    - AS 9913 - EDUARDO MONDLANE UNIVERSITY (MOZAMBIQUE) - WORKSHOP ON RENEWABLE RESOURCES, 1999-2000 (Box R3554)
    - AS 9916 - LAKE NAIVASHA RIPARIAN ASSOCIATION (KENYA) - CONFERENCE ON SCIENCE AND SUSTAINABLE MANAGEMENT OF SHALLOW TROPICAL WATERS, 1999 (Box R3554)
    - AS 9930 - TROPICAL SOIL BIOLOGY AND FERTILITY PROGRAMME {KENYA) - 17TH ANNUAL CONFERENCE OF THE SOIL SCIENCE SOCIETY OF EAST AFRICA, 1997-2000 (Box R3554)
    - AS 9933 - UNIVERSITY OF READING (ENGLAND) - GLOBAL CHANGE AND TERRESTRIAL ECOSYSTEMS FOCUS 3 CONFERENCE, 1999 (Box R3554)
    - AS 9935 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - INTEGRATED NUTRIENT MANAGEMENT, FARMERS' EXPERIMENTATION AND COVER AGRICULTURE, 1997-2000 (Box R3554)
    - AS 9936 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - ADMINISTRATIVE COSTS ASSOCIATED WITH REGIONAL PROGRAM DEVELOPMENT FROM MEXICO, 1999 (Box R3554)
    - HS 9902; AS 9911 - INTERNATIONAL LIVESTOCK RESEARCH INSTITUTE (KENYA) - WORKSHOP ON SEQUENCING THE GENOME OF PARASITE THEILERIA PARVA, 1999 (Box R3554)
  - Equal Opportunity (EO), AC.2003,039,3; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
    - EO 9604 - UNIVERSITY OF MASSACHUSETTS (AMHERST) - TWENTIETH CENTURY COMMUNITY ACTION METHODS, 1995-2001 (Box R3554)
    - EO 9703 - NEIGHBORHOOD FUNDERS GROUP - TOOL KIT ON JOBS/EMPLOYMENT; PUBLIC POLICY PUBLICATIONS, 1997-1999 (Box R3554)
    - EO 9714 - SAN FRANCISCO STATE UNIVERSITY - CALIFORNIA JOB TRENDS; CONFERENCE ON THESE TRENDS AND WELFARE TO WORK, 1997-2002 (Box R3554)
    - EO 9722 - MARTIN LUTHER KING LEGACY ASSOCIATION - JOB OPPORTUNITIES AND CREATION IN LOW-INCOME LOS ANGELES NEIGHBORHOODS, 1997-1999 (Box R3554)
    - EO 9737 - NEW YORK COMMUNITY TRUST - DONORS' EDUCATION COLLABORATIVE, 1995-1999 (Box R3554)
    - EO 9738 - NATIONAL GOVERNORS' ASSOCIATION CENTER FOR BEST PRACTICES - TEACHER LEARNING CENTERS AND PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT SCHOOLS IN STATE EDUCATION REFORM POLICY, 1997-2002 (Box R3554)
    - EO 9741 - NEW YORK COMMUNITY TRUST - NEIGHBORHOOD STRATEGIES PROJECT, 1995-1999 (Box R3555)
    - EO 9810 - NATIONAL CONGRESS FOR COMMUNITY ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT - FOURTH NATIONAL CENSUS ON COMMUNITY ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT, 1997-2002 (Box R3555)
    - EO 9811 - NATIONAL CENTER FOR ECONOMIC ALTERNATIVES - PROGRESSIVE POLICY CENTER, 1998-1999 (Box R3555)
    - EO 9812 - URBAN INSTITUTE - "ASSESSING THE NEW FEDERALISM" PROJECT, 1996-2000 (Box R3556)
    - EO 9812 - URBAN INSTITUTE - "ASSESSING THE NEW FEDERALISM" PROJECT - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1996-2000 (Box R3556)
    - EO 9813 - CORPORATION FOR ENTERPRISE DEVELOPMENT - DOWNPAYMENTS ON THE AMERICAN DREAM POLICY DEMONSTRATION, 1998-2002 (Box R3556)
    - EO 9814 - URBAN INSTITUTE - CIVIC INFRASTRUCTURE OF URBAN AREAS, 1998-2001 (Box R3556)
    - EO 9819 - INSTITUTE FOR PUERTO RICAN POLICY - MERGER TRANSITION WITH THE PUERTO RICAN LEGAL DEFENSE AND EDUCATION FUND, 1997-2002 (Box R3556)
    - EO 9820 - PUERTO RICAN LEGAL DEFENSE AND EDUCATION FUND - POLICY DIVISION, 1997-2000 (Box R3556)
    - EO 9828 - EMORY UNIVERSITY - WELFARE TO WORK IN FOUR METROPOLITAN AREAS, 1998-1999 (Box R3556)
    - EO 9829 - BARNARD COLLEGE - ECONOMIC AND CIVIC CONTRIBUTIONS OF MINORITY ENTREPRENEURSHIP IN THE INNER-CITY, 1998-1999 (Box R3556)
    - EO 9830 - NEW SCHOOL UNIVERSITY - IMMIGRANT SERVICE PROVIDERS IN LOW-INCOME NEW YORK CITY NEIGHBORHOODS AND IMPACT ON WELFARE REFORM (RESCINDED), 1998-2000 (Box R3556)
    - EO 9832 - MANPOWER DEMONSTRATION RESEARCH CORPORATION - WORKSHOP ON CONDUCTING PILOTS OR DEMONSTRATIONS IN EMPLOYMENT AND WELFARE REFORM, 1998-1999 (Box R3557)
    - EO 9838 - NAACP LEGAL DEFENSE AND EDUCATIONAL FUND, INC. - ALABAMA "BALLOT INTEGRITY", 1998-2001 (Box R3557)
    - EO 9841 - EDUCATION DEVELOPMENT CENTER - TECHNOLOGY AND COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT AND PARTICIPATION, 1998-2000 (Box R3557)
    - EO 9901 - TIDES CENTER - CIVIL RIGHTS FORUM, 1998-2002 (Box R3557)
    - EO 9906 - ECONOMIC POLICY INSTITUTE - REPORTS ON LOW-WAGE LABOR MARKET, 1996-2000 (Box R3557)
    - EO 9906 - ECONOMIC POLICY INSTITUTE - REPORTS ON LOW-WAGE LABOR MARKET - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1996-2000 (Box R3557)
    - EO 9907 - JOBS FOR THE FUTURE - CORPORATE WELFARE-TO-WORK; PAPER FOR MEETING ON WELFARE-TO-WORK IN THE U.K., 1998-2000 (Box R3557)
    - EO 9909 - THE AFTER-SCHOOL CORPORATION - IN-SCHOOL AFTER-SCHOOL DEVELOPMENT PROGRAMS, 1999-2001 (Box R3557)
    - EO 9910 - CHAPIN HALL CENTER FOR CHILDREN - IMMIGRANT SERVICE PROVIDERS IN LOW-INCOME NEW YORK CITY NEIGHBORHOODS AND IMPACT ON WELFARE REFORM, 1999-2000 (Box R3557)
    - EO 9924 - BRITISH CONSULATE-GENERAL - CONFERENCE ON WELFARE-TO-WORK IN THE UNITED KINGDOM AND LOS ANGELES, 1999-2000 (Box R3557)
- AC.2003.042 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects
  - Separated Materials, 2003:042:001
- AC.2003.047: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1995-2001; AC.2003.047; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 standard record storage box, R3561.
  - Population Sciences (PS), AC.2003.047.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - PS 9704 - ALAN GUTTMACHER INSTITUTE - SURVEY ON VAGINAL MICROBICIDES, 1996-2001 (Box R3561)
    - PS 9707 - CONCEPT FOUNDATION (THAILAND) - AVAILABILITY OF EMERGENCY CONTRACEPTIVE PRODUCTS, 1995-1999 (Box R3561)
    - PS 9712 - PLANNED PARENTHOOD FEDERATION OF AMERICA - GLOBAL PARTNERSHIP AND LEADERSHIP PROGRAM, 1997-1999 (Box R3561)
    - PS 9724; PS 9801 - TIDES CENTER - ALLIANCE FOR BARRIER ANTIMICROBIALS, 1998-2002 (Box R3561)
    - HS 9725; PS 9802 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - MEN'S FERTILITY AND REPRODUCTIVE STRATEGIES IN RURAL GAMBIA, 1997-2000 (Box R3561)
    - PS 9806; PS 9807 - FAMILY CARE INTERNATIONAL - SAFE MOTHERHOOD INITIATIVE TENTH ANNIVERSARY ACTIVITIES, 1997-1999 (Box R3561)
    - PS 9811 - BANARAS HINDU UNIVERSITY (INDIA) - DELAYED OVULATION AND POLYCYSTIC OVARIAN DISEASE, 1995-1999 (Box R3561)
    - PS 9812 - STATE FAMILY PLANNING COMMISSION (CHINA) - RURAL FAMILY PLANNING SYSTEM, 1998-2001 (Box R3561)
- AC.2003.051: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1995-2003; AC.2003.051; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, R3562, R3563.
  - BD, AC.2003.051.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - BD 9708 - PUBLIC EDUCATION FUND NETWORK - RACE AND EDUCATION IN AMERICA, 1996-1999; 2003 (Box R3562)
    - BD 9712 - WALSH, JOAN - COMMUNITY BUILDING REPORT (CONSULTANCIES), 1995-2002 (Box R3562)
    - SI 9805; BD 9802 - PUBLIC RELATIONS SOCIETY OF AMERICA FOUNDATION - NATIONAL ISSUES CREDIBILITY INDEX PILOT STUDY ON RACE AND DIFFERENCE, 1997-1999 (Box R3562)
    - BD 9803 - GROUP FOR CULTURAL DOCUMENTATION - MULE TRAIN EXHIBIT, 1998; 2003 (Box R3562)
    - BD 9805 - VISUAL ARTS RESEARCH AND RESOURCE CENTER RELATING TO THE CARIBBEAN - FOLLOW-UP ACTIVITIES ON CONFERENCE ON RACE AND CONSTRUCTION OF PUERTO RICAN IDENTITY, 1998; 2003 (Box R3562)
    - BD 9808 - NATIONAL URBAN LEAGUE - RACE RELATIONS INITIATIVE, 1998-2000 (Box R3562)
    - BD 9811- WILLIAM J. BRENNAN JR. CENTER FOR JUSTICE - MEETINGS ON VOTING RIGHTS; REDISTRICTING EDUCATION BRIEFING BOOK, 1997-2002 (Box R3563)
  - Population Sciences (PS), AC.2003.051.2; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - PS 9815 - POPULATION COUNCIL - COLLABORATIVE STUDY ON MALE FERTILITY REGULATION, 1997-1999 (Box R3562)
    - PS 9816 - CENTER FOR RESEARCH AND SERVICES RELATED TO HUMAN REPRODUCTION (BRAZIL) - SYMPOSIUM ON MICROBICIDE/BARRIER METHODS OF CONTRACEPTION, 1998-1999 (Box R3562)
    - PS 9817 - CENTER FOR REPRODUCTIVE LAW AND POLICY - WOMEN OF THE WORLD - FRANCOPHONE AFRICA PROJECT, 1998-2001 (Box R3562)
    - PS 9818 - GHANA - HEALTH (MINISTRY OF) - CONFERENCE ON HEALTH AND POPULATION ISSUES, 1998-2001 (Box R3562)
    - PS 9819 - CENTRE FOR AFRICAN FAMILY STUDIES (KENYA) - SOUTH-SOUTH NGO COLLABORATION, 1998-2000 (Box R3562)
    - PS 9821 - REPRODUCTION RESEARCH INSTITUTE - GENERAL SUPPORT, 1998-2000 (Box R3562)
    - PS 9823; PS 9901 - TIDES CENTER - ALLIANCE FOR MICROBICIDE DEVELOPMENT WORKSHOP ON CREATIVE ALTERNATIVES TO TORT REFORM, 1998-2002 (Box R3562)
    - PS 9902 - INTERNATIONAL PLANNED PARENTHOOD FEDERATION (ENGLAND) - IPPF MEDICAL BULLETIN, 1997-2001 (Box R3562)
  - Global Philanthropy (GP), AC.2003.051.3; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - GP 9903 - SYNERGOS INSTITUTE - MEETING ON WORLWIDE EFFORTS TO REDUCE POVERTY AND INCREASE ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT, 1998-2002 (Box R3563)
    - GP 9906 - UNITED NATIONS DEVELOPMENT PROGRAMME - FIRST GLOBAL FORUM ON HUMAN DEVELOPMENT, 1999 (Box R3563)
  - International Security (IS), AC.2003.051.4; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - IS 9717 - INTERNATIONAL RICE RESEARCH INSTITUTE (PHILIPPINES) - INCREASED RICE PRODUCTION IN NORTH KOREA, 1997-2000 (Box R3563)
    - IS 9720 - NATIONAL INSTITUTE OF ADVANCED STUDIES (INDIA) - TECHNOLOGY TRANSFER AND NUCLEAR COOPERATION, 1994-2000 (Box R3563)
    - IS 9724 - (INTERNATIONAL SECURITY) - PROGRAM OPERATIONS - ACTIVITIES IN ASIA-PACIFIC (INTERNATIONAL SECURITY) - PROGRAM OPERATIONS - ACTIVITIES IN ASIA-PACIFIC REGION, 1997-1999 (Box R3563)
    - IS 9805 - (INTERNATIONAL SECURITY) - SECURITY AND NUCLEAR NONPROLIFERATION IN NORTHEAST ASIA, 1997-1998 (Box R3563)
    - IS 9811 - STIMSON CENTER - "HANDBOOK OF CONFIDENCE-BUI LDING MEASURES FOR REGIONAL SECURITY" DISTRIBUTION, 1998 (Box R3563)
    - IS 9813 - OXFORD RESEARCH GROUP (ENGLAND) - MEETING ON PLUTONIUM MANAGEMENT IN BRITAIN AND NUCLEAR WEAPONS PROLIFERATION, 1998-1999 (Box R3563)
    - IS 9814 - GEORGE WASHINGTON UNIVERSITY - U.S. DELEGATION TO CHINESE MILITARY MODERNIZATION DIALOGUE, 1998-2000 (Box R3563)
    - IS 9816 - (INTERNATIONAL SECURITY) - PROGRAM OPERATIONS - NON-PROLIFERATION IN SOUTH ASIA, 1993-2002 (Box R3563)
    - IS 9819 - NAUTILUS OF AMERICA - CONNECT KOREA'S NY MISSION TO INTERNET, 1998-2001 (Box R3563)
    - IS 9825 - VIETNAM VETERANS OF AMERICA FOUNDATION - CONFERENCE ON SEEKING ALTERNATIVES TO LANDMINES, 1998-2000 (Box R3563)
    - IS 9826 - STATE OF THE WORLD FORUM - DOCUMENTARY ON PAST AND PRESENT NUCLEAR DANGERS, 1998 (Box R3563)
- AC.2003.055: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1982-2004; AC.2003.055; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 standard record storage boxes, R3564-R3567.
  - International Security (IS), AC.2003.055.1; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - IS 9827 - (INTERNATIONAL SECURITY) - LANDMINES STUDY, 1998-1999 (Box R3564)
    - IS 9833 - NAUTILUS OF AMERICA - NATO-NET, 1998-2001 (Box R3564)
    - IS 9834 - MONTEREY INSTITUTE OF INTERNATIONAL STUDIES - ASSESSMENT OF THE UNITED NATIONS SPECIAL COMMISSION, 1998-1999 (Box R3564)
    - IS 9836 - (INTERNATIONAL SECURITY) - IS PROGRAM CLOSE-OUT, 1998 (Box R3564)
    - IS 9901 - NAUTILUS OF AMERICA - DPRK RURAL ENERGY PLANNING TOUR, 1998-2001 (Box R3564)
    - IS 9905 - LIFE AND PEACE INSTITUTE (SWEDEN) - COOPERATION BETWEEN U.S. AND IRAN, 1996-1999 (Box R3564)
    - IS 9906 - STATE OF THE WORLD FORUM - NUCLEAR ELIMINATION INITIATIVE OF GLOBAL SECURITY PROJECT, 1996-1999 (Box R3564)
    - IS 9808 - NGO COMMITTEE ON DISARMAMENT, INC. - NETWORKING AND CITIZEN PARTICIPATION IN NUCLEAR NON-PROLIFERATION TREATY REVIEW PROCESS, 1999-2001 (Box R3564)
    - IS 9911 - INTERNATIONAL PHYSICIANS FOR THE PREVENTION OF NUCLEAR WAR - NATO AND NUCLEAR WEAPONS, 1998-2001 (Box R3564)
  - Special Interests (SI), AC.2003.055.2; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - IS 9917 - FUND FOR RECONCILIATION AND DEVELOPMENT - U.S. - INDOCHINA RECONCILIATION PROJECT, 1998-2001 (Box R3564)
    - SI 9523 - GIRLS INC. - ACTION FOR SAFETY PROGRAM, 1995-1999 (Box R3564)
    - SI 9614 - CENTER FOR RESEARCH AND ADVANCED STUDIES OF THE NATIONAL POLYTECHNIC INSTITUTE (MEXICO) - PRODUCTION OF CANDIDATE VACCINES IN TRANSGENIC BANANAS, 1995-2000 (Box R3564)
    - SI 9620 - CRIME AND JUSTICE FOUNDATION - SAFETY FIRST CRIME PREVENTION INITIATIVE, 1996-2001 (Box R3564)
    - SI 9723 - SOLOMON, SUSAN GROSS - RF GRANT-MAKING ACTIVITIES IN SOVIET UNION, 1922-1934, 1997-2000 (Box R3564)
    - SI 9724 - REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH TECHNOLOGIES PROJECT - EMERGENCY CONTRACEPTION IN LOS ANGELES AND SAN DIEGO, 1997-2000 (Box R3564)
    - SI 9809 - SOUND PORTRAITS PRODUCTIONS - "THE SUNSHINE HOTEL" AND "DEATH ROW DIARIES", 1998-2001 (Box R3564)
    - SI 9813 - GRADUATE SCHOOL AND UNIVERSITY CENTER OF THE CITY UNIVERSITY OF NEW YORK - SECOND GENERATION IMMIGRANTS IN NY, 1998-2000 (Box R3564)
    - SI 9820 - ROCKEFELLER FOUNDATION - COMMUNICATIONS AND SOCIAL CHANGE PROJECT, 1998-2002 (Box R3564)
    - SI 9821 - FUND FOR THE CITY OF NEW YORK - CENTER FOR INTERNET GATEWAYS TO ACCESS, EQUITY AND COMMUNITY, 1998-1999 (Box R3564)
    - SI 9822 - COUNCIL ON ECONOMIC PRIORITIES ACCREDITATION AGENCY - SOCIAL ACCOUNTABILITY 800 STANDARD WORKSHOPS, 1998-2000 (Box R3565)
    - SI 9823 - PEACE CHILD INTERNATIONAL (ENGLAND) - "CHILDREN'S INTRODUCTION TO SUSTAINABLE HUMAN DEVELOPMENT" PUBLICATION, 1997-2004 (Box R3565)
  - African Initiatives (AI), AC.2003.055.3; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - AI 9214 - UNIVERSITY OF THE WESTERN CAPE (SOUTH AFRICA) - PROGRAM IN VISITING FELLOWS IN AFRICAN HISTORY, 1992-2002 (Box R3565)
    - AI 9406 - HARVARD UNIVERSITY - "DEVELOPMENT ENCOUNTERS" WORKSHOPS, 1994-2001 (Box R3565)
    - AI 9513 - NORTHWESTERN UNIVERSITY - SEMINAR ON INTERGENERATIONAL RELATIONS IN AFRICA, 1995-1999 (Box R3565)
    - AI 9708 - UNIVERSITY OF SWAZILAND - WOMEN IN SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY IN AFRICA NETWORK, 1997-2002 (Box R3565)
    - AI 9802 - UNIVERSITY OF CAPE TOWN (SOUTH AFRICA) - EVALUATION WORKSHOP ON UNIVERSITY SCIENCE, HUMANITIES AND ENGINEERING PARTNERSHIP, 1998-2002 (Box R3565)
    - AI 9805 - INSTITUTE OF ECONOMIC AFFAIRS (KENYA) - AGENDA 2000 PLUS, PUBLICATION INFORMING ALL SECTORS ON KEY ISSUES IN KENYA, 1998-1999 (Box R3565)
    - AI 9806 - ASSOCIATION FOR WOMEN IN DEVELOPMENT - CONFERENCE ON "TRANSFORMATION FOR GENDER JUSTICE AND SOCIAL CHANGE" IN SOUTH AFRICA, 1997-2000 (Box R3565)
    - AI 9812 - WORLD BANK - WORLD LINKS FOR DEVELOPMENT (WORLD) PROGRAM, 1998-1999 (Box R3565)
    - AI 9903 - CIVICUS WORLD ALLIANCE FOR CITIZENS PARTICIPATION - AFRICAN REGIONAL ASSEMBLY ON CIVIL SOCIETY AND ERADICATION OF POVERTY IN AFRICA, 1999-2000 (Box R3565)
  - School Reform (SR), AC.2003.055.4; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - SR 9605 - NATIONAL COUNCIL FOR ACCREDITATI ON OF TEACHER EDUCATION - ASSESSMENT OF KNOWLEDGE OF TEACHER CANDIDATES, 1996-1999 (Box R3565)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2003.055.5; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - RF 84032 - BLACK SOUTH AFRICAN LEADERSHIP DEVELOPMENT, 1992-1996 (Box R3566)
    - RF 96058 #111 - AMERICAN DANCE FESTIVAL - INTERNATIONAL CHOREOGRAPHERS WORKSHOP, 1986-1999 (Box R3567)
  - Soviet Foreign Policy Studies, 855; 1.31 Cubic Feet 1 record storage box
    - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (BERKELEY) - SOVIET FOREIGN POLICY STUDIES, 1982-1999 (Box R3566)
    - UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA (BERKELEY) - SOVIET FOREIGN POLICY STUDIES - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1982-1999 (Box R3566)
- AC.2003.057: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1985-2004; AC.2003.057; 10.48 Cubic Feet 8 standard record storage boxes, R3568-R3570, R3572-R3576.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2003.057.1; 10.48 Cubic Feet 8 record storage boxes
    - RF 84032 #43 - UNIVERSITY OF CAPE TOWN (SOUTH AFRICA) - MOBILE EXHIBIT DEPICTING WOMEN IN SCIENCE AND ENGINEERING, 1997-2000 (Box R3568)
    - RF 84032 #44 - HUMAN SCIENCES RESEARCH COUNCIL (SOUTH AFRICA) - GOVERNMENT POLICIES ON PROVIDING RESOURCES TO SCHOOLS, 1997-2000 (Box R3568)
    - RF 91060 - CASSAVA: IMPROVEMENT PRIORITIES AND MOLECULAR MAPPING, 1991-1995 (Box R3568)
    - RF 91060 #14 - INTERNATIONAL INSTITUTE OF TROPICAL AGRICULTURE (NIGERIA) - HYPERTEXT DATA RETRIEVAL AND DOCUMENT SYSTEM FOR COSCA, 1995-2000 (Box R3568)
    - RF 91078 - ESSENTIAL AGRICULTURAL LIBRARY, 1991-1997 (Box R3568)
    - RF 92003 #129 - INDIAN COUNCIL OF AGRICULTURAL RESEARCH (ICAR) - DEVELOPMENT OF RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY, 1989-1999 (Box R3568)
    - RF 92004 - NATIONAL PRIORITIES FOR RICE BIOTECHNOLOGY, 1991-1995 (Box R3568)
    - RF 92006 - MACRO-LEVEL CONSTRAINTS IN AFRICAN FARMING SYSTEMS, 1989-1997 (Box R3568)
    - RF 90032 A 59 - ASSOCIATION OF RICE RESEARCH WORKERS - ORYZA (QUARTERLY JOURNAL), 1989-1999 (Box R3568)
    - RF 92045 - NATIONAL COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT INITIATIVE, 1988-1999 (Box R3569, Box R3568, R3570)
    - RF 92045 - NATIONAL COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT INITIATIVE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1988-1999 (Box R3569, Box R3568, R3570)
    - RF 93013 #514 - DUKE UNIVERSITY - RESIDENT FELLOWS AT TRIANGLE SOUTH ASIA CONSORTIUM, 1993-2004 (Box R3572)
    - RF 93013 #535 - UNIVERSITY OF TEXAS (AUSTIN) - HUMANITIES RESIDENCY FELLOWSHIPS (MERCER M, HUNTINGTON ART GALLERY), 1994-2004 (Box R3572)
    - RF 93013 #536 - FLORIDA INTERNATIONAL UNIVERSITY - HUMANITIES RESIDENCY FELLOWSHIPS PROGRAM (CUBAN RESEARCH INSTITUTE), 1994-2002 (Box R3572)
    - RF 93013 #537 - UNIVERSITY OF WISCONSIN - HUMANITIES RESIDENCY FELLOWSHIPS (CENTER FOR TWENTIETH CENTURY STUDIES), 1993-2001 (Box R3572)
    - RF 93019 - NETWORK FOR SECONDARY SCHOOL IMPROVEMENT IN THE ARTS HUMANITIES, 1985-1999 (Box R3573, R3574, R3575, R3576)
    - RF 93019 - NETWORK FOR SECONDARY SCHOOL IMPROVEMENT IN THE ARTS HUMANITIES - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1985-1999 (Box R3573, R3574, R3575, R3576)
- AC.2003.059: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1983-2001; AC.2003.059; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 standard record storage boxes, R3577-R3580.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2003.059.1; 5.24 Cubic Feet 4 record storage boxes
    - RF 93022 - BIOTECHNOLOGY CAREER FELLOWSHIPS, 1983-1999 (Box R3577)
    - RF 93028 - WOMEN FOR WOMEN'S HEALTH, 1986-1996 (Box R3577, Box R3578)
    - RF 93028 - WOMEN FOR WOMEN'S HEALTH - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1986-1996 (Box R3577, Box R3578)
    - RF 93029 #10 - WORLD HEALTH ORGANIZATION - (SWITZERLAND) - TASK FORCE ON REGULATION OF MALE FERTILITY, 1994-2000 (Box R3578)
    - RF 93029 #11 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - SHANGHAI INSTITUTE OF CELL BIOLOGY - FERTILITY REGULATION OF CONTRACEPTION-21 INITIATIVE, 1993-1999 (Box R3578)
    - RF 93038 #25 - INTERNATIONAL CENTRE FOR RESEARCH IN AGROFORESTRY (ICRAF) - SOIL NUTRIENTS DYNAMICS AND CROP YIELDS, 1992-2001 (Box R3578)
    - RF 93042 - COMMUNITY-BASED DENGUE CONTROL, 1987-1998 (Box R3579, R3580)
    - RF 93042 - COMMUNITY-BASED DENGUE CONTROL - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1987-1998 (Box R3579, R3580)
- AC.2003.063: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1993-2001; AC.2003.063; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, R3581, R3582.
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2003.063.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - RF 93045 #16 - SAHAJ SOCIETY FOR HEALTH ALTERNATIVES (INDIA) - SEXUAL BEHAVIOR AND THE TRANSMISSION OF DISEASE IN BOMBAY, 1995-2000 (Box R3581)
    - RF 93063 #80 - SHANGHAI SECOND MEDICAL UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - LEPTIN LEVELS AND REPRODUCTIVE FUNCTION, 1997-1998 (Box R3581)
    - RF 93071 - COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT INITIATIVES - USC AND ENTERPRISE FOUNDATION, 1993-1997 (Box R3581)
    - 940001-237 - ZHONGSHAN UNIVERSITY - COMPATIBILITY GENES IN RICE, 1990-1999 (Box R3581)
    - 940001-242 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - MALE STERILITY IN INDICA RICE, 1990-1999 (Box R3581)
    - RF 94010 #548 - GUADALUPE CULTURAL ARTS CENTER - U.S.- MEXICO BORDER CULTURE, 1994-2000 (Box R3582)
    - RF 94010 #548 - GUADALUPE CULTURAL ARTS CENTER - U.S.- MEXICO BORDER CULTURE - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1994-2000 (Box R3582)
    - RF 94010 #552 - CITY COLLEGE OF NEW YORK - RESIDENT FELLOWS (DOMINICAN STUDIES INSTITUTE), 1994-2000 (Box R3582)
    - RF 94010 #553 - LOWER EAST SIDE TENEMENT MUSEUM - "SWEATSHOP PROJECT", 1994-1999 (Box R3582)